export const getQuizMockResponse = () => {
  return {
    response_code: 0,
    results: [
      {
        category: "UG9saXRpY3M=",
        type: "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
        difficulty: "bWVkaXVt",
        question:
          "V2hpY2ggcHJlc2lkZW50IGVyYXNlZCB0aGUgbmF0aW9uYWwgZGVidCBvZiB0aGUgVW5pdGVkIFN0YXRlcz8=",
        correct_answer: "QW5kcmV3IEphY2tzb24=",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "Um9uYWxkIFJlYWdhbg==",
          "Sm9obiBGLiBLZW5uZWR5",
          "RnJhbmtsaW4gUm9vc2V2ZWx0",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogQm9va3M=",
        type: "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
        difficulty: "bWVkaXVt",
        question:
          "SW4gdGhlIExvcmQgb2YgdGhlIFJpbmdzLCB3aG8gaXMgdGhlIGZhdGhlciBvZiB0aGUgZHdhcmYgR2ltbGk/",
        correct_answer: "R2xvaW4=",
        incorrect_answers: ["VGhvcmluIE9ha2Vuc2hpZWxk", "Qm9tYnVy", "RHdhbGlu"],
      },
      {
        category: "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogTXVzaWNhbHMgJiBUaGVhdHJlcw==",
        type: "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
        difficulty: "bWVkaXVt",
        question:
          "V2hpY2ggb2YgdGhlc2UgbXVzaWNhbHMgd29uIHRoZSBUb255IEF3YXJkIGZvciBCZXN0IE11c2ljYWw/",
        correct_answer: "UmVudA==",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "VGhlIENvbG9yIFB1cnBsZQ==",
          "QW1lcmljYW4gSWRpb3Q=",
          "TmV3c2llcw==",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "UG9saXRpY3M=",
        type: "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
        difficulty: "bWVkaXVt",
        question:
          "RHVlIHRvIHRoZSBOYWdveWEgUmVzb2x1dGlvbiwgQ2hpbmEgYWdyZWVkIHRvIGFsbG93IFRhaXdhbiB0byBjb21wZXRlIHNlcGFyYXRlbHkgaW4gaW50ZXJuYXRpb25hbCBzcG9ydGluZyBldmVudHMgdW5kZXIgd2hhdCBuYW1lPw==",
        correct_answer: "Q2hpbmVzZSBUYWlwZWk=",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "Q2hpbmVzZSBUYWl3YW4=",
          "UmVwdWJsaWMgb2YgVGFpd2Fu",
          "UmVwdWJsaWMgb2YgVGFpcGVpIA==",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "U3BvcnRz",
        type: "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
        difficulty: "bWVkaXVt",
        question:
          "SW4gMjAxNiwgd2hvIHdvbiB0aGUgRm9ybXVsYSAxIFdvcmxkIENvbnN0cnVjdG9yJ3MgQ2hhbXBpb25zaGlwIGZvciB0aGUgdGhpcmQgdGltZSBpbiBhIHJvdz8=",
        correct_answer: "TWVyY2VkZXMtQU1HIFBldHJvbmFz",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "U2N1ZGVyaWEgRmVycmFyaQ==",
          "TWNMYXJlbiBIb25kYQ==",
          "UmVkIEJ1bGwgUmFjaW5nIFJlbmF1bHQ=",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogSmFwYW5lc2UgQW5pbWUgJiBNYW5nYQ==",
        type: "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
        difficulty: "bWVkaXVt",
        question:
          "SW4gIlB1ZWxsYSBNYWdpIE1hZG9rYSBNYWdpY2EiLCB3aGF0IGlzIHRoZSBmaXJzdCBuYW1lIG9mIE1hZG9rYSdzIHlvdW5nZXIgYnJvdGhlcj8=",
        correct_answer: "VGF0c3V5YQ==",
        incorrect_answers: ["TW9udG95YQ==", "VG9tb2hpc2E=", "TWluYXRv"],
      },
      {
        category: "RW50ZXJ0YWlubWVudDogSmFwYW5lc2UgQW5pbWUgJiBNYW5nYQ==",
        type: "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
        difficulty: "bWVkaXVt",
        question:
          "V2hhdCBzdHVkaW8gYW5pbWF0ZWQgT3VyYW4gSGlnaCBTY2hvb2wgSG9zdCBDbHViPw==",
        correct_answer: "Qm9uZXM=",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "UHJvZHVjdGlvbiBJLkc=",
          "S3lvdG8gQW5pbWF0aW9u",
          "eGViZWM=",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "QXJ0",
        type: "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
        difficulty: "bWVkaXVt",
        question: "V2hvIGRlc2lnbmVkIHRoZSBDaHVwYSBDaHVwcyBsb2dvPw==",
        correct_answer: "U2FsdmFkb3IgRGFsaQ==",
        incorrect_answers: [
          "UGFibG8gUGljYXNzbw==",
          "QW5keSBXYXJob2w=",
          "VmluY2VudCB2YW4gR29naA==",
        ],
      },
      {
        category: "U3BvcnRz",
        type: "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
        difficulty: "bWVkaXVt",
        question:
          "SG93IG1hbnkgcHJlbWllciBsZWFndWUgdHJvcGhpZXMgZGlkIFNpciBBbGV4IEZlcmd1c29uIHdpbiBkdXJpbmcgaGlzIHRpbWUgYXQgTWFuY2hlc3RlciBVbml0ZWQ/",
        correct_answer: "MTM=",
        incorrect_answers: ["MTE=", "MjA=", "MjI="],
      },
      {
        category: "R2VvZ3JhcGh5",
        type: "bXVsdGlwbGU=",
        difficulty: "bWVkaXVt",
        question: "V2hhdCBpcyB0aGUgbG9uZ2VzdCByaXZlciBpbiBFdXJvcGU/",
        correct_answer: "Vm9sZ2E=",
        incorrect_answers: ["RGFudWJl", "UmhpbmU=", "VGhhbWVz"],
      },
    ],
  };
};
